(Sheldon(at knock on door):)Oh, perhaps it's Amy
coming to her senses.
(music stops)
- What's up?
- You know,
(Leonard:)you don't need to use Sheldon
to get your way with me
(Leonard:)in a dumb
Roommate Agreement.
(Penny:)Where'd you get that from?
(Leonard:)From Amy.
(Penny:)Ugh. Amy, why did you
tell him that?
(Amy:)Because you were defending
Sheldon like you always do.
(Penny:)I don't always
defend Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Oh, yes, you do.
You know you have a weird
(Leonard:)brother-sister-Elliott-E.T.
relationship with him.
(Penny:)What about your weird
relationship with him?
(Leonard:)That's different.
(Leonard:)I'm like the little girl
in Poltergeist
(Leonard:)and he's the creepy thing
in the TV.
WOLOWITZ:
Um, guys?
(Howard:)Were there any nuts
in that food?
(Leonard:)I don't think so. Why?
Well...
just a feeling. (chuckles)
(Leonard:)It just said
"Italian sub."
(Leonard:)I had no idea mortadella
has pistachios in it.
Interesting fact:
In Italian, the "morta"
in "mortadella" means death.